You're truly, truly dear.
Life with it's sorrow, life with it's pain.
I've been to war, I love you too.
Ah, love is something to hold your time fast.
Ah, yes, it's something by your side to stand.
Dawn is so fine.
I ask for this woman to be a bride to this man.
Dearly beloved, we have gathered here in the space of this company in the presence of God
to join together in holy matrimony this man and this woman
which is honorable as declared by St. Paul among all men
is therefore not by any to be entered into unadvisably or lightly
but reverently, discreetly, advisably, soberly and in the fear of God
into this holy state these two persons present come now to be joined
if there is anyone here that can show a just cause
while they should not be lawful joined in this holy matrimony
let them now speak our forever holy peace
I will require and will charge you both
as you will surely answer at the day of judgment
when the secrets of all hearts shall be disclosed
that if either of you know any impediment
why you should not be lawful joined together in this holy matrimony
we now confess it for being assured unto you
that any persons that are joined otherwise than God's word does allow
their marriage is not lawful
but believing that you have duly considered this solemn obligation
that you are about to assume
that you are prepared to enter upon the scene
reverently, discreetly, wisely and in the fear of God
I shall propose to you the marriage covenant
you will declare the same as you join your right hand
will you take this woman to be your lawful wedded wife
to live together in this holy state of matrimony
do you promise to love, honor and cherish
in sickness and health, riches or poverty
and will forsake all others and please be only unto her
as long as you both live
I will
will you take this man to be your lawful wedded husband
to live together in this holy matrimony
do you promise to love, honor and cherish
in sickness and health, riches or poverty
and will forsake all others and please be only unto him
as long as you both live
I will
I will require a token of you
this covenant betwixt you and Sidney will always be kept
now will you join your right hand together again
upon the word of God
as I am
Almighty God
who married the first man and woman
in the garden of Eden
joining together your own creation
we do realize today
that this commission has been carried out down through the ages
until this very wedding
Father...
so let's move on over there